Finding aid for WUOM Records, 1914-1982
Bentley Historical Library
- Audio Material, 1930s-1970s
  - Sound Reels (7-inch)
    - WUOM: Original Productions
      - "To the Cornflower and the Maize,"
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #1: "The Classical Greek on the Old Frontier" ([R21A]), 1965 November 24; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-1-1]; (Part #1 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded November, 24, 1965, Broadcast January 8, 1967. "The Classical Greek on the Old Frontier" / F. Clever Bald; Robert Warner; Howard Peckham; Russell Bidlack; Philip Bursley)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #2: "The Athens of the West" ([R22A]), 1965 December 01; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-2-1]; (Part #2 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded December 1, 1965, broadcast January 15, 1967. "The Athens of the West" / Russell Bidlack; Robert Warner; F. Clever Bald.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #3: "Preachers as Teachers" ([R23A]), 1967 January 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-3-1]; (Part #3 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded on January 6, 1966, Broadcast January 29, 1967. "Preachers as Teachers" / Russell Bidlack; Robert Warner; F. Clever Bald.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #4: "Shaping a University," ([R24A]), 1966 January 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-4a-1-1]; (Part #4 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded January 20, 1966, Broadcast February 05, 1967. "Shaping a University," pt. 1 Robert Warner; E. Blythe Stason; Russell Bidlack; F. Clever Bald; Howard Peckham; Philip Bursley; Harrison Randall.)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-4b-1-2]; (Part #5 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded January 20, 1966, February 12, 1967. "Shaping a University," pt. 2 Howard Peckham; Hazel Losh; Henry Frieze Vaughn; Wells Bennett; Russell Bidlack)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #6: "Michigan at Fifty Years" ([R26A]), 1966 February 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-5-1]; (Part #6 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded February 10, 1966, Broadcast February 19, 1967. "Michigan at Fifty Years" / Russell Bidlack; Howard Peckham; A.D. Moore; Charles Sink; George Carrothers.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #7: "In Pursuit of a President" ([R27A]), 1966 April 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-6-1]; (Part #7 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded April 14, 1966, Broadcast February 26, 1967. "In Pursuit of a President" / Harrison Randall; Philip Bursley; Henry Carter Adams II; Charles Kennedy; Howard Peckham.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #8: "Literature, Science and Arts" ([R28A]), 1966 March 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-7-1]; (Part #8 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded March 10, 1966, Broadcast March 05, 1967. "Literature, Science and Arts" / Hazel Losh; William Trow; Howard Peckham; Philip Bursley; I. Leo Sharfman; William Paton.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #9: "The Glorified Blacksmith Shop" ([R29A]), 1966 June 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-8-1]; (Part #9 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded June 16, 1966, Broadcast March 12, 1967. "The Glorified Blacksmith Shop" / Henry Carter Adams II; Wells Bennett; Howard Peckham; A.D. Moore; Ruel Churchill; Samuel Dana; Roscoe Bonisteel.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #10: "Medicine at Michigan" ([R30A]), 1966 June 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-9-1]; (Part #10 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded June 16, 1966, Broadcast March 19, 1967. "Medicine at Michigan" / Helen Hebelar; Arthur Furstenberg; Henry Frieze Vaughn; Charles Kennedy.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #11: "Michigan at 75 Years" ([R31A]), 1966 June 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-10-1]; (Part #10 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded June 30, 1966, Broadcast April 2, 1967. "Michigan at 75 Years" / Howard Peckham; A.D. Moore; Ralph Sawyer; Harrison Randall; Hazel Losh; Henry Carter Adams II; Charles Sink.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #12: "Golden Age of Student Life" ([R32A]), 1966 March 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-11-1]; (Part #12 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded March 10, 1966, April 09, 1967. "Golden Age of Student Life" / Howard Peckham; A.D. Moore; Philip Bursley; Harrison Randall; Henry Carter Adams II; Charles Kennedy.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #15: "Michigan at 100 Years" ([R33A]), 1966 January 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-12-1]; (Part #15 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded January 13, 1966, Broadcast April 30, 1967. "Michigan at 100 Years" / Margaret Tracy; I. Leo Sharfman; Henry Carter Adams II; Roscoe Bonnisteel; Helen Hebelar; William Paton; Charles Sink.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #16: "A Time for Building" ([R34A]), 1966 June 25; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-13-1]; (Part #16 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded June 25, 1966, Broadcast May 7, 1967. "A Time for Building" / Preston Slosson; Charles Sink; A.D. Moore; Philip Bursley; Wells Bennett; Margaret Tracy; Roscoe Bonnisteel; William Trow; George Carrothers; Helen Hebelar.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #17: "The Yankee Rebel" ([R35A]), 1966 February 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 17)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-14-1-1]; (Part #17 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded February 11, 1966, Broadcast May 14, 1967. "The Yankee Rebel" pt. 1 / Clarence Cook Little; Margaret Tracy; George Carrothers; Henry Carter Adams II)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-14-1-2]; (Part #18 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded March 17, 1966, Broadcast May 21, 1967. "The Yankee Rebel" pt. 2 / Clarence Cook Little; Samuel Dana; William Paton; Margaret Tracy; Alexander Grant Ruthven.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #19: "Ruthven, Rackham, and Radicals" ([R37A]), 1966 April 17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-15-1-1]; (Part #19 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded April 17, 1966, May 28, 1967. "Ruthven, Rackham, and Radicals" pt. 1 / Alexander Grant Ruthven; Clarence Cook Little; George Carrothers; I. Leo Sharfman; E. Blythe Stason.)
          - [Part 2], [8738-SR-7-15-1-2]; (Part #20 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded April 17,1966, Broadcast June 04, 1967. "Ruthven, Rackham, and Radicals" pt. 2 / Alexander Grant Ruthven; Arthur Dunham; Ralph Sawyer; Charles Sink; George Carrothers; Preston Slosson; A.D. Moore; Margaret Tracy; Howard Peckham; Henry Frieze Vaughn.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #21: "Michigan at 125 Years" ([R39A]), 1967 June 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-16-1]; (Part #21 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded June 30, 1966, Broadcast June 11, 1967. "Michigan at 125 Years" / Margaret Tracy; Alexander Grant Ruthven; A.D. Moore; William Paton; Preston Slosson; Ralph Sawyer.)
        - To the Cornflower and the Maize Program #22: "The Age of the Atom" ([R40A]), 1966 July 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-7-17-1]; (Part #22 of the "To the Cornflower and the Maize" program, recorded July 14, 1966, Broadcast June 18, 1967. "The Age of the Atom" / Ralph Sawyer; Roscoe Bonnisteel; Charles Kennedy; Alexander Grant Ruthven; Harlan H. Hatcher.)
      - Abbot Memorial: Tribute to Waldo Abbot/ E.G. Burrows, et al. ([R42A]), 1964 November 18; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-8-1-1]; (Program tracing the history of the University Broadcasting Service and WUOM from 1950-60, featuring records of Bob Ufer, Donn Chown, Waldo Abbot, and others.)
      - "Union Voices" [documentary] / Daniel R. Fusfeld, host, recorded 1964-1965., 13 reels (2 programs/reel)
        (Musical anthology of the American labor movement.
        - Program #1: Beginnings, broadcast, January 13, 1965; [R43A] (Box 18)
        - Program #2: Evangelical Songs, broadcast, January 20, 1965; [R43A] (Box 18)
        - Program #3: Why Join? pt. 1, broadcast, January 27, 1965; [R44A] (Box 18)
        - Program #4: Why Join? pt. 2, broadcast, February 3, 1965; [R44A] (Box 18)
        - Program #5: The Anthracite Coal Strike of 1902 broadcast February 10, 1965, 1902-1965; [R45A] (Box 18)
        - Program #6: The I.W.W. [International Workers of the World], pt. 1., broadcast, February 17, 1965; [R45A] (Box 18)
        - Program #7: The I.W.W., pt. 2., broadcast, February 24, 1965; [R46A] (Box 18)
        - Program #8: The I.W.W., pt. 3, broadcast March 3, 1965., [R46A] (Box 18)
        - Program #9: Heritage of Violence, pt. 1, broadcast, March 10, 1965; [R47A] (Box 18)
        - Program #10: Heritage of Violence, pt. 2, broadcast, March 17, 1965; [R47A] (Box 18)
        - Program #11: The Meaning of Song to Workers, broadcast, March 24, 1965; [R48A] (Box 18)
        - Program #12: The Coal Miners, pt. 1, broadcast, March 31, 1965; [R48A] (Box 18)
        - Program #13: The Coal Miners, pt. 2, broadcast, April 7, 1965; [R49A] (Box 18)
        - Program #14: The Coal Miners, pt. 3, broadcast, April 14, 1965; [R49A] (Box 18)
        - Program #15: Girl of Constant Sorrow, pt. 1, broadcast, April 21, 1965 (Box 18)
        - Program #16: Girl of Constant Sorrow, pt 2., broadcast, April 28, 1965; [R50A] (Box 18)
        - Program #17: The Textile Workers, pt. 1., broadcast, May 5, 1965 (Box 18)
        - Program #18: The Textile Workers, pt. 2., broadcast, May 12, 1965; [R51A] (Box 18)
        - Program #19: Communism in the Labor Movement, broadcast, May 19, 1965; [R52A] (Box 18)
        - Program #20: Women in the Labor Movement, broadcast, May 26, 1965; [R52A] (Box 18)
        - Program #21: The 1930s pt. 1., broadcast June 1. 1965, 1930-1965; [R53A] (Box 18)
        - Program #22: The 1930s pt. 2., broadcast June 8. 1965, 1930-1965; [R53A] (Box 18)
        - Program #23: The 1930s pt. 3., broadcast June 15, 1965, 1930-1965; [R54A] (Box 18)
        - Program #24: Songs of Political Action, pt. 1, broadcast, June 22, 1965; [R54A] (Box 18)
        - Program #25: Songs of Political Action, pt. 2, broadcast, June 29, 1965; [R55A] (Box 18)
        - Program #26: Automation, broadcast, July 6, 1965; [R55A] (Box 18)
      - "About Books" [interview] E.G. Burrows, host; broadcast, October 1948-March 1964
        - "About Books" - Interview with John Wain (British poet) ([R56A]), 1959 March 18; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          (broadcast during academic year only)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-9-1-1]; (Two interviews with John Wain and James Ginden, Professor of English on the "Angry Young Men" writing movement in England, academia, and rhetoric.)
        - "About Books" - Interview with X.J. Kennedy ([R57A]), 1962 January 03; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-9-2-1]; (Interview with X.J. Kennedy on "Nude Descending a Staircase", "Science Fiction", touring and speaking, trends and directions in American poetry, reads "Nude Descending a Staircase.")
        - "About Books" - Interview with Denise Levertov (American poet) ([R58A]), 1962 April 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-9-3-1]; (Interview with Denise Levertov discussing women writers, teaching, writing subjects, and living in Mexico.)
        - "About Books" - Interview with Professor Samuel Graham, professor Emeritius of Economic Zoologist and Robert Bly (American poet) ([R59A]), 1963 November 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-9-4-1]; (Interview of Samuel Graham on politics and poetry. Interview of Robert Bly on translations of Scandinavian poetry.)
        - "About Books" - Interview with Viktor Frankl "Death Camp to Existentialism" ([R60A]), 1963, 1964; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-9-5-1]; (Viktor Frankl interviewed by E.G. Burroughs on the subjects of existentialism and psychiatry.)
        - "About Books" - Interview with Langston Hughes ([R61A]), [Undated]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-9-6-1]; (Radio interview with Langston Hughes discussing the "Sweet Flypaper of Life", writing themes, and his life.)
      - "Background,", 1958-1990
        (interview/panel discussion. broadcast 1958-1990. In the 1980s Background adopted a news journal format.)
        - "Background," Abortion: A Legal or Medical Problem? ([R62A]), 1962 August 01; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-10-1-1]; (Andrew S. Watson; Richard D. Judge; J. R. Julen, panelists. Radio program panel discussion about different perspectives on abortion.)
        - "Background," "The American Woman: Her Education, Her Family, Her Career" ([R63A]), 1963 December 18; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-10-2-1]; (Louise Cain; Gretchen Groth; Hope Davis; Deborah Friedman; Helen Tanner; Radio panel discussing contemporary women's issues.)
        - "Background," The Feminine Mystique ([R64A]), 1964 May 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-10-3-1]; (Panel discussion discussing Betty Friedan's book "The Feminine Mystique." Panelists are: Betty Friedan and Shirley Mattern Smith.)
        - "Background," The Peace Corps and the University of Michigan ([R65A]), 1964 November 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-10-4-1]; (Radio program about Sargent Shriver, includes excerpts of his Peace Corps speech; with Harlan Hatcher; Sargent Shriver; et al.)
        - "Background," [Panel discussion about the October 1965 sit-in at the Ann Arbor Draft Board and resultant draft status reclassification and legal suit] ([R66A]), 1966 March 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-10-5-1]; (Discussion of the Selective Service and Draft Board, Conscientious Objectors, and sit-ins. Panelists are: Paul Kuyper; Philip Hart; et al., Fred Hindley, announcer.)
        - "Background," Classified Research at the University of Michigan ([R67A]), 1967 October 27; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-10-6-1-1]; (Part 1; Panel discussion about Classified Research at the University of Michigan. Gordon J. Van Wylen; Walden Rhines; A. Geoffrey Norman; Richard Mann; Roger Rapaport; Eric Chester.)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-10-6-1-2]; (Panel discussion about Classified Research at the University of Michigan. Panelists are: Robert C. Elderfield, Thomas G. Giese, William E. Porter.)
        - "Background," ["Student Radicalism"] ([R69A]), 1967 December 31; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-10-7-1]; (Panel moderated by Willard Haber. Panels are: Stanley M. Swinton; Michael Dann; Roger Rappaport. Roger Rappaport reads from Paul Goodman's speech at the National Security Industrial Association; ends at 30:27 with unrelated content at 34:43 to end on Czechoslovakia's government.)
        - "Background," [5 students reply to Lyndon B. Johnson's State of the Union address], broadcast Special of the Week ([R70A]), 1968 January 23; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 18)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-10-8-1]; (Student replies to Lyndon B. Johnson's State of the Union, guests include: Harriet Freedman, Harriet Rosenberg, Lynn Fagen, Randal Frost, Walter Shapiro.)
      - "Commentary,", 1961 (Box 19)
        (viewpoints on topics of contemporary interest presented by University of Michigan faculty], broadcast October 1954-? Preceded by regular news commentary program featuring Preston Slosson. 1 reel retained)
        - [Preston Slosson's final program] Analysis and summary of critical world issues as they might be viewed from the White House, August 21, 1961; [R71A] (Box 19)
      - "Conservation Report" [interview/news digest] broadcast, October 1956-October 1972
        (2 reels retained (2 programs per reel))
        - "Action by Citizens Groups a Way to Guard Local Water Needs" / Lyle Crane (University of Michigan Department of Conservation), October 2, 1962; [R72A] (Box 19)
        - "Lumber Quality Begins in the Woods" / John Carow (University of Michigan Department of Forestry), October 16, 1962; [R72A] (Box 19)
        - "Michigan Produces Rich Variety of Christmas Trees" / Kenneth P. Davis (University of Michigan Department of Forestry), November 27, 1962; [R73A] (Box 19)
        - "Deer Still Need Management" / A.B. Cowan (University of Michigan Department of Wildlife), December 4, 1962; [R73A] (Box 19)
      - "Eleventh Hour" [arts interview] / E.G. Burrows, host, broadcast, January 1968-September 1982 (Box 19)
        (3 reels retained)
        - "Eleventh Hour" Interview with Joyce Carol Oates ([R76A]), 1968 May 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-11-1-1]; (1968 interview with Joyce Carol Oates discussing her writing and experiences.)
        - "Ragtime, Tin Pan Alley, and the University of Michigan Varsity Show" / Gerald Marks discusses and sings works of Seymor Simons and other University of Michigan alumni with popular music careers, February 13, 1968; [R74A] (Box 19)
        - North Campus Interview: U-M School of Music rehearsal for upcoming "Contemporary Directions" concert / George Wilson; Sydney Hodkinson; et al., February 24, 1968; [R75A] (Box 19)
      - "Especially for Women" [interview/panel discussion], broadcast, October 1949-July 1951
        (1 reel retained)
        - "Especially for Women" Eleanor Roosevelt, Marie Miller, Waldo Abbot; Dorothy Thompson ([R77A]), 1950; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-12-1-1]; (Show broadcast October 1949-July 1951; Eleanor Roosevelt discusses China, panelists are: Marie Miller and Waldo Abbot, Dorothy Thompson, Baldwin, et al. in conjunction with University of Michigan Religion in Life Week. Recorded January 30, 1950)
      - "Hello, Alumni" [report/interview/documentary] / T. Hawley Tapping, host, 13 reels
        - "Hello, Alumni" Rose Bowl Win and Willie Heston ([R78A]), 1951 January 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-1-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program, hosted by T. Hawley Tapping discussing Rose Bowl Win, 1950; Bill Fleming, Bob Ufer, Don Dufek, et al., January 15, 1951 Willie Heston, November 23, 1951)
        - "Hello, Alumni" Alexander G. Ruthven ([R79A]), 1954 January 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-3-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program hosted by Bill Stegath and T. Hawley Tapping, interviewing President Ruthven.)
        - "Hello, Alumni" Henry Sanders [Professor Emeritus of Latin] ([R80A]), 1954 January 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-4-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program hosted by Bill Stegath and T. Hawley Tapping, interviewing Henry Sanders.)
          - [Part 2], [8738-SR-13-4-2]; mp3 file; (Ending announcement for Hello, Alumni program, no new content.)
        - "Hello, Alumni" John L. Brumm, ([R81A]), 1954 February 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-5-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program hosted by Bill Stegath and T. Hawley Tapping, interviewing John L. Brumm.)
        - "Hello, Alumni" [Professor Emeritius Edgar M.] Durfee [of the Law School]([R82A]), 1954 January 25; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-6-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program hosted by Bill Stegath and T. Hawley Tapping, interviewing Professor Emeritius Edgar M. Durfee.)
        - "Hello, Alumni" Guest: C.O. Wisler [Professor Emeritus of Engineering] ([R83A]), 1954 January 26; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-7-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program hosted by Bill Stegath and T. Hawley Tapping, interviewing C.O. Wisler, Professor Emeritus of Engineering.)
        - "Hello, Alumni" James B. Edmondson [Dean Emeritus of the School of Education] ([R84A]), 1954 January 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-8-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program hosted by Bill Stegath and T. Hawley Tapping, interviewing James B. Edmondson, Dean Emeritius of the School of Education.)
        - "Hello, Alumni" Philip Bursley [Professor Emeritus of Department of Romance Lanugages] ([R85A]), 1954 January 29; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-9-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program hosted by Bill Stegath and T. Hawley Tapping, interviewing Professor Emeritius Philip Bursley.)
        - "Hello, Alumni" [Frank E.] Robbins [retired Assistant to President of the University] ([R86A]), 1954 March 18; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-10-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program hosted by Bill Stegath and T. Hawley Tapping, interviewing Frank E. Robbins retired Assistant to the President of the University.)
        - "Hello, Alumni" Matt Mann [Coach of Varsity Swimming Team] ([R87A]), 1954 March 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-11-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program hosted by Bill Stegath and T. Hawley Tapping, interviewing Matt Mann, Coach of the Varsity Swimming Team.)
        - "Hello, Alumni" Samuel T. Dana [Dean Emeritus of School of Natural Resources] ([R88A]), 1954 March 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-12-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program hosted by Bill Stegath and T. Hawley Tapping, interviewing Samuel T. Dana, Dean Emeritius of the School of Natural Resources.)
        - "Hello, Alumni" [Anthology]: Voice of Yost / Fred J. Lawton; Hello, Alumni #2 / Bob Morgan ([R89A]), [Undated]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 15 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-13-13-1]; ("Hello Alumni" program hosted by Bill Stegath and T. Hawley Tapping, Fred J. Lawton as the "Voice of Yost.")
      - "I Open the Door" [readings of children's literature] / Virginia Michalak, reader, 1964., 2 reels
        (broadcast October 1963-April 1966 during academic year only)
        - "The Green Christmas" from Henry Huggins recorded September 17, 1964: original broadcast December 2, 1963, 1963-1964; [R90A] (Box 19)
        - Excerpt from The Hobbitt original broadcast, December 9, 1963 (Box 19)
        - "The Man with the Red Eyes" from A Wrinkle in Time, recorded, October 6, 1964; [R91A] (Box 19)
          (original broadcast October 26, 1964)
      - "Record Collector" [music anthology] / Warren Good, host, 1 reels
        (broadcast November 1949-September 1975.)
        - Christmas Show, December 23, 1960; [R92A] (Box 19)
      - "Special of the Week" [speech/panel discussion]